Guide to the University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg, Visual Images, 1889-2019 UPG.RG.60
ULS Greensburg
- Prints (PR), 1969-2014; V.
  - Sports Awards Banquet [Later Sports Awards Reception/Ceremony], 1998-2001 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 11, Box 2, Shelf 8, Box 3)
    1998 [Spring] 1998 [Fall] 1999 [Spring] 1999 [Fall] 2000 [Spring] 2000 [Fall] 2001 [Spring] 2001 [Fall]
    See UPG.RG.21 Ser.: Sports Awards Ceremony & Reception for Programs Spring 2000-Fall 200
  - Sports Awards Reception/Ceremony, 2002-2007 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 11, Box 2, Shelf 8, Box 3)
    2002 [Spring] 2002 [Fall] 2003 [Spring] 2003 [Fall] 2004 [Spring] 2005 [Spring] 2005 May 22, 2005 2006 Apr. 2, 2006 2006 [Spring] May 12, 2006 2007, April 16. First Annual All Sports Banquet. [Prints include: Chi Alpha Sigma (National College Athletics Honor Society) Juniors, Seniors; Female Faculty Athletics Representative Award; Male Faculty Athletics Representative Award; Male Athlete of the Year; Female Athlete of the Year.]
    See UPG.RG.21 Ser.: Sports Awards Ceremony & Reception for Programs 2000-2008.
  - Spring Carnival, 1996-2005 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 8, Box 3)
    1996 1998 1999 2000 2001 2005
  - Spring Fling, 2002 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 8, Box 3)
  - Staff Awards Luncheon, 1997-2009 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 8, Box 4)
    1997 1998 2000 2001 2002 2003 2004 2005 2006 2007 2009 [on Compact Disc]
    For programs, etc., See UPG.RG.52 Subject Files. Ser.: Staff Awards Recognition Program.
  - Staff Receptions [Annual Independence Day Picnic and Croquet Tournament], 1987-2006 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 9, Box 1)
    Picnic. Sept., 1987 Picnic. July 4, 1998 Picnic. July 4, 2001 Picnic. Sept., 2001 Picnic. July 4, 2002 Picnic. July 4, 2005 [held on June 30, 2005] Picnic. July 4, 2006 [held on June 29, 2006] Includes a CD-R.
  - Stained Glass Window, August 1999 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 9, Box 1)
    UPG Seal. Chambers Hall. [made by Terry Bengel; glass created and donated by Youghiogheny Opalescent Co., Connellsville, Pa. Installation.]
  - Student Activities Board. Executive Board, 2009-2010 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 9, Box 1, Shelf 11, Box 2)
    2009/2010 Aborno, Hope; Flower, Kegan; Kyle, Meghan; Moody, Angela; Seitz, Danielle; Strain, Sally; Strain, Sara; Valentine, Jana; Watka, Dana; Zacur, Amanda.
    2009/2010 Group Photo.
    See also Oversize for Group Photo.
  - Student Activities Fair, 1999-2004 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 9, Box 1)
    1999, Fall
    2001, Fall
    2002, Fall
    2003, Fall
    2004, Fall
  - Student Awards, 1995-1998 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 11, Box 2, Shelf 9, Box 1)
  - Student Government Association, 2002-2010 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 11, Box 2, Shelf 9, Box 1)
    Salvation Army Presentation [Feb., 2002]
    Officers 2003/04
    Student Government Association. Senate. 9/11/07.
    Student Government Association. House of Representatives. 9/26/07.
    Student Government Association. Senate. 2009/2010 Group Photo.
    Student Government Association. Executive Board. 2009/2010. Group Photo.
  - Student Leaders, 2005-2006 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 9, Box 1, Shelf 11, Box 2)
    1/23/05
    10/6/05
    10/31/06
  - Student Life, 1980-2002 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 11, Box 2, Shelf 9, Box 1)
    1980's
    1990's
    undtd.
  - Student Midnight Breakfast, 1997-1998 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 9, Box 1)
    12/9/97
    4/14/98
  - Student Photographs, 1995-1997 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 9, Box 1)
    Holly Asbee with Michael Zipko 12/8/95
    Jena Demore with Sean Vanyo 12/8/95
    Evan Schermer 11/5/97
  - Summer Camp (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 9, Box 1)
    Cheerleaders, Dance Team, Color Guards [undtd]
  - Tennis (Men's), 2001-2012 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 9, Box 2, Shelf 11)
    2003/04 Roster 2004
    2005/06 Roster 2006
    2006/07 Spring 2007
    2007/2008
  - Tennis (Women's), 1997-2012 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 9, Box 2, Shelf 11)
  - Tennis Courts, 1997-1998 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 9, Box 2)
    Tennis Courts behind McKenna Hall removed when new tennis courts constructed in the 1990's. Construction. New Courts. 1997. 1998. Dedication. Reception. New Courts. Aug., 1998.
  - Tosatto Plaza/Tosatto Drive, 1997 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 9, Box 2)
  - Traffic Light at Main Entrance (Mt. Pleasant Rd.) to UPG Campus, 2002 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 9, Box 2)
  - "Tuna" Singers From Spain, April 3, 2002 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 9, Box 2)
  - Turow, Scott, October 7, 1998 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 9, Box 2)
    Author. UPG Cultural Series.
  - Twins, October 2002 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 9, Box 2)
    Twins on UPG Athletic Teams. Brian and Chris Gesinski, Tennis (Men's); Jen Sutlic, Basketball (Women's) and Dee Sutlic, Volleyball (Women's); Maggie and Melissa Weiss, Volleyball (Women's).
  - Twirlers, 1997-1998 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 9, Box 2)
  - UPG Ambassadors, 1998-2004 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 9, Box 3)
    Undtd
    1999 Feb. 15; 1999 Apr. 11
    2002-2003
    2003-2004
  - UPG Emerging Leaders Development Series [UPG ELDS]. Graduation (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 9, Box 3)
  - UPG Leadership Conference, October 23, 2004 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 9, Box 3)
    6th Annual
  - UPG Organizations' Fair, August 30, 2000 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 9, Box 3)
  - UPG Pageant [Miss UPG Pageant], 2002-2003 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 9, Box 3)
    2002, Dec. 5 [1st] 2003, Dec. 5
  - UPG Performance Collective, 1999-2004 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 10, Box 1, Shelf 11, Box 2, Box 3)
    The Adding Machine. Mar. 15-18, 2001
    Beyond Therapy. Nov. 10-12, 2000
    Fool for Love. Apr. 1-3, 2004. [n.b. Negative only. See: UPG.RG.60 Visual Images. Negatives. Miscellaneous. UPG Performance Collective. Production. Fool for Love.]
    The Lion in Winter. Nov. 7-10, 2000
    Memorandum. Nov. 12-14, 1999
    R.U.R. (Rossum's Universal Robots). Nov. 20-22, 2003
    Suburbia. Mar. 21-23, 2002
    Such Foolish Affected Ladies. Nov. 6-9, 2002
    Talking With. Mar. 21-22, 2003
    The UPG Regional One-Act Festival: The Little Red Gate and Not Lightly Chosen. Sept. 13-15, 2001.
    The Visit. Mar. 25-26, 2000. See: Oversize Prints.
    On CD-R: UPG Student Productions, Spring 2000-Fall 2002: The Visit, Beyond Therapy, The Adding Machine, The Lion in Winter, Suburbia, Such Foolish Affected Ladies
  - UPG Players, November 20-21, 1997 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 9, Box 3)
    Two one act comedies by Anton Chekov: The ProposalL, The Bear. Cast: The Proposal, N, McWhinney, Judy Vollmer, Bill Pamerleau. Cast, The Bear, Sayre Greenfield, Mark McColloch, Joanne Viano, Mary Beth Spore. Includes negatives.
  - UPG Press, 1998 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 9, Box 3)
  - UPS Check Presentation, March 26, 2001 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 9, Box 3)
    Given to UPG in recognition of participation by UPG students in the UPS training program.
  - Variety Shows (Student), 1978-1981 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 9, Box 3)
    Produced by Dr. L. Beeson. [1978-81?]
  - Volleyball (Women's), 1997-2012 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 11, Box 2, Shelf 9, Box 3)
    2004/05 Roster 2004
  - Volleyball Court (Outdoor), 1998 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 9, Box 3)
  - Volleyball/Basketball Courts (Outdoor), 1999 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 9, Box 3)
    Scope and Content Notes`
    View of courts. Installation of light stands.
  - Wildlife [UPG Wildlife] (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 9, Box 3)
    Mallards
    See also: UPG.RG.60 FD 1 Wildlife [UPG Wildlife]
- Slides (SL), 1960-2002; VI.
  N.B. The slide collections are housed in the verticle file cabinets.
  - Carousels, 1998-2002; 1.
    Carousel 1 2000 June. Subjects include: various campus buildings; pictures taken during the Summer Orientation Academic Registration (S.O.A.R.) campus tour of June 2000. 30 slides.
    Carousel 2 Late 1990's, early 2000's. Subject: student housing; dormitory life. 41 slides
    Carousel 3 2000 June - August. Subjects include: various campus buildings; pictures taken during the Summer Orientation Academic Registration (S.O.A.R.) campus tour of June 2000. 53 slides.
    Carousel 4 2000 June. Subjects include: Chambers Hall; pictures taken during the Summer Orientation Academic Registration (S.O.A.R.) campus tour of June 2000. 72 slides.
    Carousel 5 2000 June. Subjects include: Millstein Library; pictures taken during the Summer Orientation Academic Registration (S.O.A.R.) campus tour of June 2000. 43 slides.
    Carousel 6 2000 June. Subjects include: McKenna Hall; pictures taken during the Summer Orientation Academic Registration (S.O.A.R.) campus tour of June 2000. 38 slides.
    Carousel 7 2000 June. Subjects include: various campus buildings; UPG mascot. 42 slides.
    Carousel 8 Late 1990's, early 2000's. Subjects include: Millstein Library; Chambers Hall; Rick Fogle; student housing; dormitory life. 60 slides.
    Carousel 9 ca. 1998. Subjects include: College Hall; Millstein Library; student housing; dormitory life. 76 slides.
    Carousel 10 2000 June. Subjects include: Smith Hall; pictures taken during the Summer Orientation Academic Registration (S.O.A.R.) campus tour of June 2000. 58 slides.
    Carousel 11 2000 June. Subjects include: Smith Hall; pictures taken during the Summer Orientation Academic Registration (S.O.A.R.) campus tour of June 2000. 59 slides.
    Carousel 12 2000 June. Subjects include: Millstein Library; pictures taken during the Summer Orientation Academic Registration (S.O.A.R.) campus tour of June 2000. 60 slides.
    Carousel 13 2000 June. Subjects include: Bridge from Powers Hall; pictures taken during the Summer Orientation Academic Registration (S.O.A.R.) campus tour of June 2000. 21 slides.
    Carousel 14 2002. Subjects include: student housing; dormitory life. 125 slides.
    Carousel 15 2001-2002. Subjects include: student housing; dormitory life; pictures taken during the Summer Orientation Academic Registration (S.O.A.R.) campus tour of June 2001. 136 slides.
    Carousel 16 2002. Subjects include: student housing; dormitory life; pictures taken during the Summer Orientation Academic Registration (S.O.A.R.) campus tour of June 2002; Mark McColloch. 137 slides.
    Carousel 17 2002. Subjects include: student housing; dormitory life. 123 slides.
    Carousel 18 2002 July. Subjects include: student housing; dormitory life. 134 slides.
    Carousel 19 2002 June. Subjects include: pictures taken during the Summer Orientation Academic Registration (S.O.A.R.) campus tour of June 2002. 59 slides.
    Carousel 20 1998-2000. Subjects include: Pitt men's basketball games; Pitt women's basketball games; pictures taken during the Summer Orientation Academic Registration (S.O.A.R.). 63
    - Carousels, 1998-2002 (File-cabinet 8, Drawer 1, Drawer 2)
  - Metal Slide Storage File, 1960-1997; 2.
    1960's 11 slides
    1973 15 slides
    1974 44 slides
    1976 59 slides
    1977 58 slides
    1979 32 slides
    1982 10 slides
    1983 6 slides
    1984 209 slides
    1985 32 slides
    1986 401 slides
    1987 97 slides
    1988 96 slides
    1989 87 slides
    1990 67 slides
    1992 266 slides
    1993 33 slides
    1995 106 slides
    1996 60 slides
    1997 67 slides
    Undated 22 slides
    Bldgs. - Common Fac. Bldg. a.k.a., Student Center now Chambers Hall 8 slides
    Bldgs. Fac. Office Bldg. 1 slide
    Bldgs. Lynch Hall 26 slides
    Bldgs. Millstein Library 25 slides
    Bldgs. Vogel 1 slide
    Misc. 32 slides
    - Metal Slide Storage File, 1960-1997 (File-cabinet 8, Drawer 4)
  - Slide Binders, 1983-2000; 3.
    SB1: April 1983 - October 1992 + undated ca. early 1990's. Subjects: campus scenes, campus buildings, students on campus taken by Herb Ferguson. 282 slides.
    SB2: April 1984 - July-December 2000 + undtd. Subjects: buildings on campus, Summer Orientation Academic Registration (S.O.A.R.), students on campus, admissions. 499 slides.
    SB3: Humanities Day 1986 (57 slides); Fall Festival 1986 (26 slides); Miscellaneous 1983-1985 (17 slides); Miscellaneous undtd/uncaptioned (69 slides)
    - Slide Binders, 1983-2000 (File-cabinet 8, Drawer 3)
- Video Cassettes (VC), 1979-2006; VII.
  NB: A number of these videocassettes have been transferred to a DVD format. For print copies use landscape mode. See UPG.RG.60 Visual Images. DVD24 UPG Campus History. faz 12/11/12
  - Campus History, July 26, 1994 - October 11, 2002; 1.
    UPG.RG.60.VC.I.3 Cassell, Dr. Frank A. Installation as Third President of the University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg, March 25, 1998.
    UPG.RG.60.VC.I.4 Oral History of the University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg. Dr. Patricia M. Duck, Director of the Library, initiated the oral history project to document the history of the University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg in May, 1997. Dr. Mark D. McColloch conducted the interviews, except where noted, in sessions which each lasted between 60 and 90 minutes. The interview sessions were videotaped and since the project's inception in 1997, the following interviews have been conducted:
    UPG.RG.60.VC.I.4h Pt. I, Pt. 2 Chambers, Dr. George Ferguson. Aug. 13, Oct. 11, 2002. 2 VC See also: UPG.RG.60.DVD.24.A.9
    UPG.RG.60.VC.I.4a Chew, Dr. Paul. 1997, June 4. 1 VC See also: UPG.RG.60.DVD.24.A.4
    UPG.RG.60.VC.I.4b McWhinney, Dr. Norman N. 1997, May 21. 1 VC See also: UPG.RG.60.DVD.24.A.2
    UPG.RG.60.VC.I.4c Nicoletti, Dr. Guy M. 1997, May 28. 1 VC See also: UPG.RG.60.DVD.24.A.3 [n.b. UPG.RG.60.VC.I.4c found to be defective, 02/10/2020. Use UPG.RG.60.DVD.24.A.3] faz 02/11/2020 UPG.RG.60.VC.I.4d Poke, Dr. Carl F. 1997, June 18. 1 VC See also: UPG.RG.60.DVD.24.A.5
    UPG.RG.60.VC.I.4e Reilly, Dr. Donald T. 1997, July 16. 1 VC UPG.RG.60.DVD.24.A.7
    UPG.RG.60.VC.I.4g *Rossetti, Dr. Guy. 1998, July 20. 1 VC See also: UPG.RG.60.DVD.24.A.8
    UPG.RG.60.VC.I.4f Scanlon, Dr. Norman W. 1997, June 25. 1 VC See also: UPG.RG.60.DVD.24.A.6 *Interview conducted by Dr. Patricia M. Duck
    UPG.RG.60.VC.I.5 Segura, Prof. Juan. Interview with Prof. Juan Segura of Guanajuato, Mexico, first UPG Fullbright Scholar, Jan.-Apr., 2000. Interview conducted by Dr. Mark McColloch, Associate Vice President for Academic Affairs, on 19 April 2000. See also: UPG.RG.51 Biographical File -- Segura, Juan.
    UPG.RG.60.VC.I.2 UPG Campus History. Interview with Mary Lynch Quinn, July 26, 1994. See also: UPG.RG.60.DVD.24.A.1 Includes a 12 page holograph aide-memoire, i.e., notes, prepared by MLQ for the interview; sometimes called a transcript. Photocopy. Another copy in UPG.RG.51 Biographical File -- Lynch Family.
    See also: UPG.RG.61.C.14, Audio Cassette of "Tour of Lynch Hall" by Dr. Albert Smith, Sept. 28, 1986; UPG.RG.61.C.15, Audio Cassette of "Interview with Kathryn Lynch", August 1986; UPG.RG.61.C.16, Audio Cassette of "Interview with Thomas Lynch", July 22, 1986 [JK was UPG Gardener and former chauffeur to the Lynch Family].
    - Campus History, July 26, 1994 - October 11, 2002 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 1)
  - Dedication Ceremonies, August 16, 1989 - November 13, 2007; 2.
    Carillon (Ferguson Carillon: The Edith Ferguson Chambers Carillon). VC II. 1 See also: UPG.RG.60.DVD.24.C Dedication, September 9, 1995. 2 copies
    Chambers Hall Dedication (renaming of Common Facilities Building to Chambers Hall), June 20, 1997. VC II. 2 See also: UPG.RG.60.DVD.24.C
    Children's Collection (The Joan Chambers Children's Collection) Dedication, September 9, 1995. 2 copies. VC II. 1 See also: UPG.RG.60.DVD.24.C
    Clock (Campus) Dedication, October 13, 1995. VC II. 3 See also: UPG.RG.60.DVD.24.C (For audio cassette, see UPG.RG.61.C1.)
    Common Facilities Dedication, August 16, 1989. VC II. 4 See also: UPG.RG.60.DVD.24.C
    Mary Lou Campana Chapel and Lecture Center, Dedication Ceremony, Tuesday, November 13, 2007. For DVD of Dedication Ceremony, See: UPG.RG60.DVD.8.
    Millstein Library (Fanny K. Millstein Library) Dedication, May 5, 1995. VC II. 5 See also: UPG.RG.60.DVD.24.C Robertshaw Hall Dedication, August 22, 1989. VC II. 4 See also: UPG.RG.60.DVD.24.C
    Tosatto Plaza and Tosatto Drive Dedication, June 27, 1997. VC II. 6, VC II.7 See also: UPG.RG.60.DVD.24.C
    "Upward to the Light". The Dr. Paul Albert Chew Memorial Window. Dedication. May 14, 2005. See also: UPG.RG.52 Ser.: Art Works: "Upward to the Light". The Dr. Paul Albert Chew Memorial Window. Dedication. See also UPG.RG.60 Ser.: Prints. Art Works. The Dr. Paul Albert Chew Memorial Window. Dedication.
    N.B. see also UPG.RG.52 Subject Files -- Buildings and UPG.RG.52 Subject Files-- Programs (Dedication). See also UPG.RG.61 for Audio Cassettes of Campus Clock Dedication and Millstein Library Dedication.
    - Dedication Ceremonies, August 16, 1989 - November 13, 2007 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 2, Shelf 1)
  - Events, September 18, 1983 - March 28, 2003; 3.
    A. Fall Festival 1983, September 18. VC III. A. 1 See also: UPG.RG.60.DVD.24.B.2 1991, September 22. VC III. A. 2 See also: UPG.RG.60.DVD.24.B.2
    B. Humanities Day 2nd Annual, 1983 VC III. B. 1 a, b, c See also: UPG.RG.60.DVD.24.B.3
    B.1a, Program of Events; B.1b, Candid Shots; B.1c, Scene from Midsummer Night's Dream UPG Student Production. 3rd Annual, 1984, April 12. VC III. B. 2 N.B.: no VC III.B.3
    10th Annual, 1991, April 18. Awards Ceremony. VC III. B. 4
    11th Annual, 1992, April 15. Awards Ceremony. VC III. B. 5
    12th Annual, 1993, April 20. Awards Ceremony. VC III. B 6
    13th Annual, 1994, April 22. Awards Ceremony. VC III. B. 7
    14th Annual, 1995, April 21. Diane Lise Perez Burke, History of Flemenco. VC III. B. 8
    15th Annual, 1996, April 19. VC III. B. 9 See also: UPG.RG.60.DVD.24.B.3
    16th Annual, 1997, April 18. VC III. B. 10 See also: UPG.RG.60.DVD.24.B.3
    16th Annual, 1997, April 18. Art Entries. VC III. B. 11
    17th Annual, 1998, April 17. Awards Ceremony. VC III. B. 12 Art Entries. VC III. B. 12b
    C. Greensburg Bicentennial/Victorian Picnic. Sept. 12, 1999. VC III. C (For additional information, see UPG.RG.52 Subject Files--Greensburg Bicentennial and UPG.RG.60 Visual Images--Prints--Homecoming, 1999--Greensburg Bicentennial.)
    D. Honors Convocation See also UPG.RG.52 Subject Files--Honors Convocation 2000, March 1 (2nd) VC III.D.1 2001, March 21 (3rd) VC III.D.2 2002, April 5 (4th) VC III.D.3 2003, March 28 (5th) VC.III.D.4
    E. Cultura, La. 2002 Cultura, La. The Life and Times of Leonardo da Vinci [Leonardo and the High Renaissance]. Reception and Dinner, Jan. 19, 2002. VC III.E. See also: UPG.RG.60.DVD24.B.1
    F. Cultura, La. 2003. A Paris. Dinner and Reception. 1/18/03. VC III.F.
    N.B. For Videocassettes or DVDs of La Cultura Lecture Series, See: UPG.RG.60 Videocassette VC VIII Talks, Lectures, Speeches or UPG.RG.60.DVD.
    - Events, September 18, 1983 - March 28, 2003 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 2)
  - Forums, Symposia, Seminars, Workshops, February 28, 1992 - March 3, 2004; 4.
    Active Learning Forum, February 15, 1993. Participants: VC IV. 1 Tony Boldurian, David Champagne, Diane Marsh
    Alcohol and Legal Liability, April 9, 1991. Participants: VC IV. 2 Hon. Donald E. Wieand, Judge, Superior Court of Pennsylvania; Hon. Joseph A. Del Sole, Judge, Superior Court of Pennsylvania; Hon. Gilfert M. Mihalich, Judge, Court of Common Pleas, Westmoreland County; Mike Rubinoff, Attorney and Associate Professor, UPG; Moderator, Robert Blum, Attorney.
    Criminal Justice Day, March 25, 1993. 3 cassettes. Guest Speaker, VC IV. 3 a-c Former U.S. Attorney General, Ramsey Clark (VC IV. 3c); Panel discussion, "Drugs, Gangs and Drive-By Shootings," with participants: Judge Donetta Ambrose, Court of Common Pleas; District Attorney John Driscoll; Commander Ronald Freeman of the Pittsburgh Police; Commander Leonard, Washington PA State Police/Troop A; J. Daniel McGregor, State Correctional Facility; Attorney Richard Galloway; UPG Assistant Professor Gilbert Duncan IV; Dr. Mary Jane Dugan, Assistant Professor of Administration of Justice, UPG, Moderator.
    Faculty Seminar Series, University of Pittsburgh, Oakland, 1982-83. 1982 September 30. VC IV.4a The Art of Lecturing.
    1982 October 26. VC IV.4b Games, Simulation and Role Playing. Panelists: Lawrence Knolle, Irene R. Joos, Donna L. Hoffmeister. Moderator: John M. Roberts.
    1983 January 17. VC IV.4c Pitt's International Programs. Panelists: Paul Masoner, Burkart Holzner, Keith McDuffie. Moderator: Robert L. Wolke.
    1983 March 17. VC IV.4d The Third Mission: Service. Participants: Robert P. Newman, David E. Epperson, Albert Van Dusen.
    1983 February 24. VC IV.4e The Discussion Mode of Teaching. Participants: R. Owen, R. Marshall, H. Goscilo, B. Harris-Schenz.
    1983? February 23. VC IV.4f Microcomputers in Teaching. Panelists: Thomas A. Dwyer, J. Fred Gage, Alan M. Lesgold. Moderator: Wayne E. Baughman.
    Faculty Who Question the [Gulf] War, 1991. VC IV .5 Participants: L. Beeson, R. Blevins, M. Gardner, D. Gibson, R. Koeske, S. Lau, J. Lokay, D. Marsh, M. McColloch, S. Murabito, G. Rossetti, J. Vollmer, V. Waxwood.
    Granada, Forum on Issues Relating to, November 11, 1983. VC IV.6 See also: UPG.RG.60.DVD.24.B.5 Guest speakers: Dr. Richard Blackett, Professor of History and Black Studies, University of Pittsburgh Oakland and a Caribbean Specialist; Dr. Donald Gibson, Assistant Professor of Sociology, UPG; Russell Rowe, Editorial Editor of the UPG student newspaper. Participant: J. Vollmer.
    The Impact of the Health Care Crisis on Our Region. Seminar, Mar. 3, 2004. VC IV.10 Sponsored by the Westmoreland Chamber of Commerce and the UPG Advisory Board. [Explores the rapidly changing costs of healthcare from the perspectives of the legal, medical, insurance and business communities. Panelists include: Dr. Martin A. Murcek, Greensburg allergist and former president of Highmark, Inc.; Michael Pepperney of Kennemetal Compensation and Benefits. Moderator, Prof. Alan Meisel, JD, Director of the Center for Bioethics and Health Law, Univ. of Pgh., School of Law. Series part of the Westmoreland Forum. See also: UPG.RG.27 Ser.: News Releases, 2/6/04; UPG.RG.52 Ser.: Westmoreland Forum.]
    Moving Toward a National Infrastructure. Teleconference, February 28, 1992. Participant: J. Dennis O'Connor. VC IV.7
    OSHA Training, August 25, 1993. VC IV.8
    Pittsburgh Area College Consortium. Alcohol Abuse on College Campuses. [undated] VC IV.9
    Saving Kids from the System: Town meeting on Juvenile Justice. VC IV.11 Pennsylvania Futures Commission on Justice in the 21st Century. Westmoreland County. October 30, 2001. See Also: UPG.RG.27 News Releases. News Release 10/15/01, "UPG To Host Juvenile Justice Town Meeting".
    - Forums, Symposia, Seminars, Workshops, February 28, 1992 - March 3, 2004 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 3, Shelf 2)
  - Graduation [Commencement] Ceremonies, April 28, 1990 - April 30, 2016; 5.
    1990, April 28. VC V.1
    1991, April 27. VC V.2
    1992, April 25. VC V.3
    1993, May 1. VC V.4
    1994, April 30. VC V.5
    1995, April 29. VC V.6
    1996, April 27. VC V.7
    1997, April 26. VC V.8
    1998, April 25. VC V.9
    1999, May 1. VC V.10
    2000, April 29. VC V.11
    2001, April 28. VC V.12
    2002, April 27. VC V.13
    2003, Apr. 26. VC V.14
    2004, Apr. 24. VC V.15
    2005 Archives lacks this year.
    2006, April 29. VC V.17
    2007, April 28. DVD 7.1
    2008, April 26. DVD 7.2
    2009, April 25. DVD 7.3
    2010, May 1. DVD 7.4
    2011, Apr. 30. DVD 7.5
    2012, Apr. 28. DVD 7.6
    2013, Apr. 27. DVD 7.7
    2014, Apr. 26. DVD 7.8
    2015, Apr. 25. DVD 7.9
    2016, Apr. 30. DVD 7.10
    See also: UPG.RG.60.DVD.24.B.4
    N.B. See UPG.RG.07 for Graduation Programs.
    - Graduation [Commencement] Ceremonies, April 28, 1990 - April 30, 2016 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 4, Shelf 3)
  - Individuals, February 28, 1992 - August 29, 2001; 6.
    Chambers, Dr. George Ferguson Retirement Dinner, November 22, 1996. 2 copies. VC VI.1